freehoroscopesastrology.com 2019-03-20

# Free Horoscopes Astrology Privacy Policy

|  | 

* * *

Free Horoscopes Astrology respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies to information collected at the freehoroscopesastrology.com web site (Free Horoscopes Astrology) and its subdomains, owned and operated by the Millenium Multimedia Corporation, 751 NW 108th Ave, Plantation FL 33324. We may amend this statement at any time. Such amendments will apply from the time of publication forward.

Visitor Tracking

We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Your browser’s help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used by Free Horoscopes Astrology to track user preferences while the user is visiting the website. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing. Persistent cookies may be used by Horoscope Services to store, for example, whether or not you want your password remembered, or other such information. Cookies used on our websites do not contain personally identifiable information.

Log Files

Like most websites, Free Horoscopes Astrology uses log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate throughout the site, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in the log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to personally identifiable information.

How We Use This Information

We may use the personally identifiable information collected to contact customers regarding products and services and, to the extent the User has agreed to it, by our trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners or their trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. We will not in any way share this information with any other third party either for free or by selling it, unless you specifically authorize such disclosures. We may also use this information for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our websites, services, marketing, advertising and sales efforts.

Disclosure of Information

Free Horoscopes Astrology may also disclose aggregate, anonymous, data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. In such cases, statistical information only will be disclosed and personally identifiable data will be kept strictly confidential. In case Free Horoscopes Astrology changes ownership, the information collected from users may be transferred to the new owners.

Free Horoscopes Astrology may from time to time engage third parties (e.g. Horoscope Services/shop.freehoroscopesastrology.com), including its own subsidiaries and affiliated companies, to preserve, analyze or otherwise store or manipulate data received by Free Horoscopes Astrology from its customers. In all such cases, such third party service providers will be required to treat all such data with the same degree of care as us, and they will be prohibited from disclosing such data to any other person or party, except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy.

Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on users visiting our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Special Offers and Updates

Free Horoscopes Astrology customers, members and registered users will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and possibly one or more newsletters. Out of respect for the privacy of users, we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement, if, for instance, a service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

Legal Disclaimer

Though every effort is made to preserve your privacy, Free Horoscopes Astrology may need to disclose personal information when required to by law. If it is deemed necessary that such action needs to be taken, We will comply with judicial proceedings should a court order or legal process be served on Horoscope Services.

The Free Horoscopes Astrology Website contains links to other sites and advertisements created by third parties and third party websites. Please be aware that we are not in control of or responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and third parties. You are encouraged to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. The Free Horoscopes Astrology Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by us.

Maintenance of Information

The information provided to Free Horoscopes Astrology is saved indefinitely and may be stored on one or more databases directly or indirectly maintained by Free Horoscopes Astrology. We utilize industry standard security measures to protect the confidentiality of the information. Although Free Horoscopes Astrology cannot guarantee that any loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur; every effort is made to prevent such occurrences. Any other particularly sensitive information, such as payment details collected for commercial transactions, is encrypted prior to transmission by you to us.

Your Responsibility

You are responsible for the security of your account numbers and/or passwords. Make sure you keep them in a safe place and do not share them with others.

Always remember to log out after your session ends, to ensure that others cannot access your private personal information. You should take this precaution even if you are not using a public computer, such as at a library or internet café, but even when using your private computer in your home.

[

### Personal Horoscope Birth Chart Readings

](mailto:freehoroscopesastrology@millenniummultimedia.net)

Our in-depth personal astrology reports and personalized horoscopes are all about YOU, based on your zodiac birth chart. Birthday horoscopes, based on your birth place, birth date and time are the most accurate readings available. You'll be amazed by these in-depth astrology forecasts and personal zodiac interpretations. Available online and for immediate download without obligation, so grab your [free natal chart, birth chart interpretation and free personality profile](https://www.freehoroscopesastrology.com/free-zodiac-birth-chart.aspx) today. If you like the sample readings, you'll be thrilled with the full length astrology predictions and reports, on sale now!

**Favorite Astrology Quote:** "You are a child of the universe, no less than the trees and the stars.  You have a right to be here.  And whether or not it is clear to you, no doubt the universe is unfolding as it should." - Max Ehrman

|  |
